[cheering]
[applause]
[music]
[cheering]
[applause]
[music]
[cheering]
>> Ladies [cheering] and gentlemen,
please welcome to the stage Monique
Marvez. [cheering]
>> [music]
[cheering]
[applause]
>> Good evening, everybody.
>> [cheering]
>> Thank you. Thank you. Thank [applause]
you. Thank you.
I'm delighted. I hope you guys like the
dress.
>> [cheering]
>> Thank you. I dressed up for you. It's
tighter than a frog's ass in flight. I
I'm a meaty woman. I like my food. I'm
not going to lie to you. I really like
my food. Don't trust skinny chicks.
Physical pleasures are physical
pleasures. If a woman doesn't like a
good meal, there's a pretty good chance
she's not going to be into a who's your
daddy. You know what I mean? There's a
There's a direct correlation. Watch a
woman eating barbecue. If she sucks the
meat off the bone and it's so clean you
can put it back in the cow, you want
that one, all right? I uh
Yeah.
Yeah. I know a few things about
relations. I fail fail fail
relationships. That's how you learn. You
screw stuff up. You just mess it up
whole I got to just mention your
hair situation on your face, sir.
I I don't usually go right at somebody,
but that's a bold statement. You You
what I mean? That's a crazy kind of I
used to look like that and then I met a
waxer. I uh yeah I I
Cuz that's that's a
You got That's not even a That's NOT A
BEARD OR MUSTACHE or goatee. Like how do
you describe that? That's like a facial
vagine. That's uh yeah that's
That's I've never seen fa- It just
stopped me. I don't mean to be
distracted. It stopped me dead in my
tracks. So uh yeah yeah craziness. I am
Yeah so I've been married and divorced
three times. I just like to get the bad
news out. Just get it out. Just get it
out so nobody judges me. I don't count
Yeah What What do you mean wow? Like
Really? I get a wow? Can I just explain?
I don't count my first husband, okay? I
don't count I don't cuz I'm Hispanic and
Catholic and you know I'm I married my
high school sweetheart. You know that's
what you do when you're young. It's
going steady with paperwork. I was an
idiot. I was a pendeja.
That's what my people do. You marry the
first man you see naked. That's what you
broke it, you bought it. You know,
stupid.
Stupid.
And I tried to save that marriage. I
even went to a marriage counselor when
it failed cuz my mom was like, "Meha,
did you go to counseling?" I tried to
save it. I went to a marriage counselor.
Let me tell you something. If a couple's
in marriage counseling, it's cuz the guy
[\h__\h] up and the woman caught him. CUZ
MEN IT'S TRUE. MEN DON'T WANT TO GO TO
COUNSELING. LET ME CLUE YOU IN, LADIES.
MEN DON'T EVEN LIKE TALKING TO US ABOUT
their feelings. They sure don't want to
talk to a stranger and they don't want
to pay for the privilege. IF A MAN IS
TALKING TO A STRANGER ABOUT his
feelings, it involves a hand jam, okay?
That's what it involves.
It's a happy ending discussion. It's not
about feelings, you know? So yeah, I
married my high school sweetheart.
That's what I did. It runs in the
family. And then my second marriage
You're pointing at her. She married her
high school sweetheart. It uh a while
back cuz No I mean I don't mean to Yeah
I'm
I'm not
I mean hey, LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ME WITH THE BETTY
CROCKER HAIR. You know some stuff. You
know what I mean? That's The worst
prejudice in the world is ageism. People
look at an older lady and they think,
"Oh my goodness, watch yourself. She's
been looking at weiners since before I
was alive."
She was looking at all hairy winners.
She wasn't even Yeah, guys trim now. Did
you know that, ma'am?
It's not like back in your day where it
looked like a buzzard hanging out of his
nest on a cliff wall.
Is that you guys?
>> [applause]
>> 54 years? Holy cow. I don't know if you
guys know this, but when guys get older
that it matches. You know what I mean?
Like this guy looks like Santa Claus
with a long nose down there. That's a
That's what we got work. 54 years and
you're happily married. I am so crazy
jealous. I wish you were my parents. I
really do.
>> [applause]
>> So embarrassing.
No, I'm not the fourth. Bite your
tongue. Let's uh we'll get What I wish
they were I really do. I wish What
stability. Do you know WHAT MY CHILDHOOD
WAS? MY PARENTS were multiple marriers.
See, I got it from them. My dad was
married five times, my mother four. They
married each other twice. My third
stepmother was a retired Mexican hooker
who evidently was the Brett Favre of
coochie and could not stay retired. And
uh my second stepfather turned gay,
okay?
I think you bring about what you think
about. My mother used to constantly live
in mortal fear that her husband, who was
younger than her and attractive, kind of
hot, we all wondered what the hell, but
who knew? You know, I mean, it they
didn't match. Little did we know. My My
stepfather did not leave my mother for a
younger, thinner woman. He left my
mother for an older, fatter man.
YOU CAN'T MAKE THAT UP. He came roaring
out of the CLOSET ON A HOG. I
I'M NOT CALLING HIS BOYFRIEND A HOG. IT
WAS A HARLEY, SIR. He rides a
motorcycle, okay? You guys, he rides in
the gay pride parade of New York in
assless chaps saying, "Give me my
dignity." It's a good time.
I keep in touch with him. He's an
amazing person. He's so sweet, but he's
not my stepfather anymore. And and
things change, you know, getting back to
my second marriage, I I that one was
going to work. I'm not going to lie to
you, cuz we had a lot of chemistry. We
just had a lot of chemistry. We had
nothing in common. We fought like crazy.
And you can't marry someone for
chemistry, cuz chemistry won't overcome
when a guy's sleeping and all you can
think to yourself is, "Shit, he's
breathing." You know what I mean? Like
that. You can't You got to leave. You
got to leave when that happens. You got
to leave.
Yeah. And then there was such
ambivalence about getting married the
third time. I really didn't want to do
it. I didn't want to do it. I was in my
late 30s and my girlfriend started in on
me, "You're going to want a baby. You're
going to want a baby." Like that. Like
it was the H1N1 virus was going to come
over me and I was going to have this
baby lust that was going to make me
crazy. And I was like, "Oh my goodness,
yes, I do want a baby." I DON'T KNOW WHY
THEY TRICKED me because I'm ambivalent
about children. They frightened me. They
They made me succumb to fear. Cuz
honestly, kids are little and you trip
on them. You know, they're just in your
way. I'm clumsy. MY DOGS KNOW, "GET
UNDER THE COUCH, MOMMY'S BEEN DRINKING."
YOU KNOW, THEY KNOW.
I DON'T DRINK A LOT, but once you open
the bottle of Boone's Farm, who's
closing that up? You know? It's uh Yeah,
and kids are like little stinky beggars.
They follow you around. They do. They
just follow you. Apple juice, apple
juice, apple juice. Like that. LIKE
LITTLE DRUGS. Apple juice. You know?
I got nieces. I know.
AND THEY COME OUT OF YOUR PRIVATES. THEY
KIND OF PLAY THAT DOWN. PEOPLE PLAY IT
DOWN the way KIDS COME INTO THE WORLD. I
mean, I'M NOT BRAGGING ABOUT Snap the
Wonder Clam, but you know, she served
me, you know.
I'm not saying I'm THIS LADY'S LIKE,
"SNAP! OH MY GOODNESS." YOU KNOW. YEAH.
I like you. I like this whole crowd. You
guys This lady on the aisle, we want to
get a hold of her in the animal print.
Don't turn around. You're an old [\h__\h]
You're the good kind.
>> [applause]
>> I want to cruise with you, sister.
Oh, yeah. You're a good time. You're a
good time.
Yeah, kids they do they they You know,
and and the thing is about that, you
know, the thing is about that, I'm a
chicken. People come up to me and go,
"You're a comedian. That's so scary."
I'm like, "Do you have kids?" They're
like, "Yeah." I'm like, "That's way
scarier. That's way scarier." They come
They got big heads. I got nieces. They
got big heads. That just sounds so
painful and frightening, you know? Like,
what do you You sit there I was sitting
there I shouldn't say this, but my
cousin Kim, her kid has a giant head.
And I'm sitting there at the first
birthday just, you know, stroking the
kid on the head sitting there and I'm
like,
"How long was it till you weren't
whistling like a Coke bottle down
there?"
She said, "I'll let you know."
WHY DID I FALL FOR THIS? WHY?
BUT I THOUGHT, you know, maybe maybe I
would want a baby. And again, where I
come from, you don't just have a kid.
You get married and you have a kid. So
stupid. So I I succumbed. I I married my
third husband thinking I was going to
want a kid. And then about 10 minutes
into the marriage, I was like, "Are you
kidding me?" Like, let me TELL YOU
SOMETHING. GOD wants you to go to the
promised land. It's you that make him
take you through the bad neighborhoods.
My third marriage was Compton.
That's unbelievable stuff. So yeah, my
my my third marriage was a disaster. I
got out of it. I dated for a little
while and that was an even bigger mess
cuz I'm honest, you know? And evidently
dating involves lying.
I am not a good liar. I'm awful at it. I
tell people, "My name is Monique. I put
the ho in honesty. I uh
Yeah, it's true. I'm totally I just put
it out there. I just, you know, So I Me
and my girlfriends I have a group of
girlfriends. And we went through a
period of time where we just kept
picking bad stupid men. You know, what I
call disclaimer men. You know when you
got to call ahead and explain to your
friends he hasn't been sober very long,
you know what I mean? You
You got to call ahead and pave the way
for the disclaimer men. Pretty bond
girl, you've dated one of those? Like,
he Yeah, he had a rough childhood. His
uncle had wandering phalanges. You know,
you got to explain it to people? Yeah.
That'll sink in in the car. Oh my god,
Adio. I uh
Yeah, so so yeah, I dated the disclaimer
men forever and you were always having
to explain things to people. It was so
embarrassing. And and then when you
break up with them, you just objectify
them. Like every woman has nicknames for
her ex. Dog of Satan, you know, that was
one of mine. I had a dog of Satan. Yeah.
Guys never have nicknames for exes.
They're just all psycho [\h__\h] or
Yeah.
THE GUYS ARE LIKE, FINALLY WE'RE GETTING
SOMEWHERE.
I'M ON YOUR SIDE, GUYS. A LOT OF GUYS
WON'T COME SEE a lady headliner cuz like
she's a man basher. I love men. Don't
let this talk about my three divorces
frighten you. I love men. I am
straighter than Yoko Ono's pubic hair. I
love men.
I love men.
I love men. Married and divorced three
of them. Not your fault. I was a bad
picker. Not your fault. I'm delighted
now. I love my life now. I have an
amazing boyfriend now. He's amazing. I
love him like crazy. He's way younger
than me.
>> [cheering]
>> He's crazy young. Oh, yeah. People go,
HOW YOUNG IS YOUR BOYFRIEND? FOR HIS
BIRTHDAY, I took him to Legoland. I uh
yeah, he's
he's young.
Let's face it, people make assumptions.
You see an older woman, you see a
younger man, you figure I'm riding him
like a Harley in second gear. But it
didn't
and I am. But I didn't start out that
way.
We were actually friends. We actually
hung out. We had a good time. And to say
that I'm a cougar
implies that he is prey. To say that oh,
THAT MAKES HIM SOUND LIKE a wounded
fawn, like some little idiot SITTING
THERE LIKE, "OH, NOT THE WINNER!"
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
CRADLE ROBBER. SEE, THEY CALL WOMEN
NAMES. IF YOU'RE GOING TO CALL ME A NAME
CUZ I'M WITH A YOUNGER MAN, call me what
I am, sore.
>> [cheering]
>> Do not [\h__\h] with me, little dude.
There'll be nothing left to you but hair
gel and a fake Rolex. Do not
in a fetal position crying for your
mother. I love my life now. We have fun.
Do you Do you have a girlfriend, sir?
You do. Is she older than you?
31 and you're what? 15? 17? It works out
perfectly. You're just here to let your
fluids build back up.
Yeah.
That's a good deal. You know why? Cuz
when women get older, we get less crazy.
I'M GOING TO TELL you right now, guys,
you with the long hair back there, raise
your hand.
I love everything about you.
You are clueless.
You can see. I'm going to give you some
clues. What's your name, long hair?
Jason. Listen up right now. You have a
woman in your life?
She's crazy.
You know why? Because she reads
magazines. She reads Jane and Marie
Claire and Cosmo and Allure.
Yeah, he's like, "Oh my god." YES, I
KNOW. ANYTHING WITH A KARDASHIAN on the
cover is going to [\h__\h] up your life,
Jason.
You snatch that [\h__\h] right out of her
hand.
It's true.
It's [\h__\h] Those magazines freak you
out. THE BEDROOM TRICK THAT DRIVES them
wild. They've been selling these things
for 40 years. 40 years. Cosmo magazine,
every cover, how to get a man, what to
do with them when you have them, how to
get rid of them when you're done. Every
month. Every month, 40 YEARS, MONTH
AFTER MONTH. The bedroom trick that
drives them wild. You know the bedroom
trick that drives them wild, JASON? SHOW
UP.
THAT'S THE TRICK.
>> [applause]
>> IT'S TRUE.
SHE'S BEEN SHOWING UP FOR 53 YEARS. LOOK
AT THIS GUY.
54. He's count How often DO YOU KNOW A
MAN THAT KNOWS HOW LONG HE'S BEEN
MARRIED AND THE ANNIVERSARY? He's like,
"54. We don't do it often, but when we
do, it's good."
We get biscuits when we're done.
She's hitting him. He didn't even SAY
ANYTHING. SHE'S HITTING HIM.
You're telegraphing that I'm horny. It's
okay. IT DOESN'T MATTER. ISN'T it good?
Isn't it good now that you're older? You
don't give a damn.
Yeah, cuz when you're young you worry.
Young women, Jason, are all about
validation, approval, support. Look at
me, approve of me, am I pretty enough?
That's what they're like. When you're
older, self-confidence is more rare than
physical beauty. You know why my dude's
into me? Because I walk up to him on
Fridays and I just say, "Baby, do me any
way you want. When you're done, squeegee
me and bring me a jelly donut." Like
that.
THAT'S GOOD TIMES.
>> [cheering]
>> THAT'S GOOD TIMES.
>> [applause]
>> IT'S RIGHT, JASON.
And you LEARN HOW TO TALK TO A MAN when
you get older. When you're younger, when
you're younger you just want to control
and manipulate a man. That's what young
women want to DO BECAUSE WE'RE SMALL
PHYSICALLY. SO, we try to control
mentally what we cannot control
physically. THAT'S WHY WOMEN CONSTANTLY
manipulate and nag at men. I read in a
magazine article, women nag at men
because unconsciously they feel that the
man is a reflection of them. It's a
reflection. They nag at you because when
you're out in public, they think
someone's going to say like, "How the
hell did Jane let Jason go out with that
long greasy hair like that?"
It's true. You're fine. Your lady needs
to leave you alone. If you have time to
nag at a man, you have time to shag a
man, all right?
And that's HOW YOU MOTIVATE THIS GUY WAS
LIKE, "YEAH."
Would you like me to repeat that, sir?
You love that. I'm going to repeat that.
If you HAVE TIME TO BOSS and manipulate
a man, let me explain something to you.
Men are rebellious by nature. The more
you nag at them, the less they're going
to want to do that. They're rebellious.
They're overgrown children. Look, this
guy's nodding, "Yes, yes, yes, Monique."
What's your name, sweetheart? Okay, if I
say something wrong, you correct me,
okay? Listen up, gorgeous. What's your
name?
Veronica. I can see you're bossy, all
right? I can spot it. Listen to me,
Veronica. This is you. I'm telling you
right now, clean the garage. I mean it.
Clean the garage. She's laughing. Oh my
god, she's psychic. Clean the garage.
Clean the garage. That's not how you get
a man. That's not how you communicate.
You want to have a clean garage, lean
over to him and smile and go
I'll blow you if
Would you like that?
>> [applause]
>> He doesn't Would you like that, sir?
Sure you would. And while you're at IT,
THROW IN A BUNNY RUB, OKAY? Don't be
lazy.
It's morally reprehensible to use sex to
manipulate a man. However, however,
there is nothing wrong with positive
bunny reinforcement.
If a man does something you like, let
him know. That's how they want you to
reward them. They like that cuz they're
sensitive balls.
Get in there like you mean it. Change
the wrinkle pattern, sister.
Yeah. I can see you guys have a good sex
life. I'm going to get back to you some
more cuz you know what? You give me
hope. You make me super happy. No, you
really do. Me and me and my young dude,
we're happy. We're going to go the
distance. We are. I'm doing everything
to stay young. I'm working out. Yeah.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> I'm not Yeah.
I'm working out.
Because the truth is when you fall in
love with another person, you're
actually falling in love with yourself,
you know? That's why that person does it
for you because they bring out the best
in you. They want you to take care of
yourself. I eat healthier, you know, I I
I take shots in the face. That uh
That used to have a whole different
meaning 10 years ago. I uh
That's uh
I lost you, animal print.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
That That means Botox, ma'am. I'm not
doing anything nasty, you
I Yeah.
But you do, you give me hope. I think
this is going to be it. I think we're
going to go the distance and and and and
you young people see when you're really
young in your 20s and you look at your
parents you're thinking like oh my God
they're like let me tell you something
God's going to play a trick on you.
Jason you're never going to think you're
old ever ever at any time will you think
you're old. 85-year-old people watch the
Today show to see who Willard Scott is
wishing a happy birthday. They're like
you see that 102-year-old [\h__\h] in Selma
oh that's an old lady that woman in
Alabama that's an old lady. Me I'm 85
I'm still kicking ass. Me you have the
same age you know what I mean? Yeah.
Your parents call you and say Jason let
us know when you're coming home.
They don't care where you are they don't
care if you're drinking or what YOU THEY
DON'T CARE. THEY JUST DON'T do it as
often and they don't want you walking in
on them all right Jason?
Paints a picture don't it Jason?
Sexually active. My dad was unbelievable
such a womanizer so embarrassing. I
remember my stepmother called me one
night in the middle of the night
high-pitched squeal very angry cuz she
caught my dad. She snuck up behind him
in stocking feet and caught my dad. I
don't want to be rude but he was uh
pleasuring himself in front of the
computer.
You know what you know what I mean right
Jason? Roughing up the suspect?
IT'S SO FUNNY GUYS TALK ABOUT THESE
things and they make jokes about it.
They all have names for beating the
bishop shaking the bacon punching the
munchkin tending to the swinging sirloin
shucking Bubba shaking hands with the
unemployed.
It's a big game for dudes.
And no matter HOW MANY I SAY A GUY WILL
COME UP TO ME AND TELL me another one
cuz you guys are playful with that
business. You never hear a woman say
yeah I got bored I figured I'd just sit
around and stroke the road kill. You
don't see that.
We're so cryptic and shy. When you get
older you get braver but but young women
are so weird about that sort of stuff.
So my stepmother calls me in the middle
of the night screaming cuz she catches
my dad looking at something nasty on the
internet and you know and I was what do
you say to her? But then there's a part
of me thinking that blood is in my veins
that's good times right there.
That's excellent cuz my mom's not that.
My mom's Hispanic and Catholic and lives
in denial, even when her husband was
obviously gay. My mom was like, "He's
having a gay situation."
She's having a gay That's what she said.
How do you me How do you turn gay? I'm
like, "Mom, you don't turn gay. It's not
like real estate. Like it used to be a
Whole Foods, now it's a homo." It's not
like that.
She's so polite and in denial. She won't
come to a show like this. My mom sees me
like this through her fingers like that
when she watches me. She's like, "Why do
you have to talk like that, mija? Why?"
She just freaks out. "Are you wearing
Tony's?" She worries all the time.
She worries all the time I'm going to be
in a car wreck.
I don't have the heart to tell her I
don't wear them. I wear tight dresses. I
can't wear Tony's, they'll show. I keep
a pair in my glove compartment.
If I'm ever in a car wreck, I'll throw
them out in the grass. "Mommy, I had
them on."
"But the car hit so hard they flew off
on impact."
It's true. THAT'S WHY I GOT MARRIED THE
first time. I didn't want to disappoint
my mom and I was having premarital sex
with my high school sweetheart and I was
embarrassed. And that's so weird cuz all
these years later, now that I'm single,
I mean, I have a boyfriend, but you
know, I'm not married, my mother tells
me, "Mija, if you were just to turn up
pregnant, you know, just turn up. Like I
fell asleep in the garden department of
Home Depot. Someone stuck a bulb in
there or something, you know?"
Men love women different than women love
men. When a man loves a woman, he loves
you of a piece. It's a It's He can't
explain it. It's a lower chakra dog
sniffing chemical thing that grabs them
by the short hairs and renders them
[\h__\h] When a man
When a man loves you, he can't EVEN TELL
YOU WHY. HIS BEST FRIEND WILL CALL HIM
ON THE PHONE AND GO, "THAT'S A BAD
WOMAN." EVERY man in this room, I'm
going to look right at you cuz your
friends hang with strippers and don't
tell me no, okay?
What's your name, beard boy?
Huh?
Mike, how are you, baby?
Good. Have you ever had a friend fall in
love with a completely inappropriate and
heinous horrible woman?
And there wasn't a damn thing you you
do, huh? Now, you just had to sit there
with A BOTTLE OF JACK AND SOME
BAND-AIDS.
VODKA, that's right.
Call him up on the phone. Dude, she's a
bipolar stripper, raging alcoholic with
a giant cold sore and a little kid.
It's like, I got to go, Mike. I'm
watching the kid right now. I'm uh
She's working. She's spinning on the
pole right now. I uh I'll get Right?
When a man loves a woman, it's the most
beautiful thing in the world. It's of a
piece. They want to protect you. They
can't explain it. They just want you in
their cave. And I was fortunate enough
that my guy really He picked me. That's
what I say. He's a cougar slayer. I
didn't I didn't stalk and pick him. He
picked me. Cuz ladies, this sounds kind
of old-fashioned, but in order for a
relationship to work, the man must
choose the woman. If you want it to go
long-term, if you want a man to be a
man, you got to let the man pick you.
You in the plaid shirt.
You're a young man. Very young. Totally
young. Are you You got hair and
everything, right? You're like
I don't want TO FREAK YOU OUT AND wreck
your puberty or anything. You're all
good, right?
Well, as young as you are, as young as
you are, is that your girlfriend?
I can tell cuz you're all manly. Even
though you're a young little dude,
you're holding her hand, you're
possessive, you've got that manly pose.
I'm a man. I got eight hairs, but
they're manly.
They're manly hairs and I'm drinking
milk. So, I uh
yeah. You picked her, didn't you?
Cuz any woman can get any man she sets
her heart to. Cuz men are lazy.
It's true. If you stalk a man, if you
want him This is wrong and I shouldn't
tell you this.
But it's not like it's nothing I haven't
done when I was younger.
If you want to get a guy, all you got to
do is let him move in with you because
they are lazy. And all you have to do is
tell them, "Okay, if we're not getting
married, you're going to have to move."
A man will rather marry you than move
his [\h__\h]
And it's wrong.
Because if you had to talk a man into
you, you will spend the rest OF YOUR
LIFE TALKING him into you. Doesn't work
that way. When a man picks you, he loves
you, he wants you, AND DON'T WHINE YOUR
WAY OUT OF number one. That's what women
do. They whine THEIR WAY THE GUY WANTS
YOU AND AND HE'S BOUGHT you and you give
him all the reasons WHY HE SHOULD TAKE
YOU BACK, YOU KNOW? MEN DON'T DO THAT.
Men do not apologize for themselves. You
tell the woman, "You look fabulous
today. I should have gotten a pedicure."
He's not even looking at your feet. He's
not even looking at your head. He's
looking right around this region right
here, okay?
You never see a guy standing there in
his underpants going, "I really should
work out more. Really. My tighty whities
are extra tighty and not so whitey." No,
they don't DO THAT.
WOMEN APOLOGIZE FOR THEMSELVES. WE TALK
MEN OUT OF US. IF A MAN loves you,
that's the most beautiful thing in the
world. My friend Andrew came up to me.
He goes, "I want you to talk to Carol."
That's the way men know they can talk to
me. I said, "Why?" She goes, "She used
to wear all the hot lingerie, you know,
the garter belts. We used to do it all
the time, crazy positions. Now she's all
self-conscious. She's all nervous. She
wears like T-shirts, turns the light
out. It's a bummer. Talk to her." So, I
said, "Carol, what's the deal?
What's the deal? Why have you stopped
wearing the lingerie?" And she's like,
"Well, I've had two kids. I've gained a
couple of pounds. I have some varicose
veins over here. I have a little bit of
hail damage."
I said, "Are you kidding me? That man
adores you. HIKE YOUR CHUNKY ASS UP AND
LET HIM POKE YOU STANDING. COME ON, GET
WITH THE PROGRAM."
He loves you. They don't see us the way
we see us. They see us the way they
found us. Don't talk them out of you. If
a man loves you, that's the most
beautiful thing in the world. See, when
a woman loves a man, we can talk
ourselves into a man. And women are mean
sometimes. They go, "Men only want young
women." You hear that all the time. "Men
only want young women. They only want
thin women. They only want blind women."
I am not young. I am not thin. I am not
blonde. I got the cutest boyfriend ever.
But men want I do. He's He's gorgeous. I
might show him to you a little later.
He's around. I uh
But But I say a man wants what he wants
because men are forced into a sexual
honesty that women are not. The woody
does not lie.
A man cannot go in the bathroom and go,
"She's from a good family. She sews all
her own clothes."
He'll just look up all limp and go,
"Send fingers and tongue and I'm not
moving." You know?
I'm going to tell you right now, when a
man wants you, he wants you. He does,
you know? Can I ask you a personal
question, sir?
You, 54 years? I mean, I I understand,
but do you got to pop a lot of the blue
pills to do the business, SIR?
NO BLUE PILLS. HA! PROOF! PROOF! PROOF!
SAY IT INTO THE CAMERA. NO BLUE PILLS. I
WANT IT IN THE CAMERA. AND SHE'S NODDING
OFF PROUD. OH, NO.
And I don't need any help, either. I'm
moist as a front cake. Oh, no.
Weeds.
I'll show you the train track marks on
my ass right now.
No blue pills. Beautiful. Cuz you know
what? The woody doesn't lie. I think in
a lot of cases, not all cases,
[screaming] BUT A LOT OF CASES, THAT
BLUE PILL SAYS, "I HATE your guts, but I
love this house."
Beautiful. You made my night. You guys
give me hope. Adopt me, please.
So, I'm going to get back to you, little
blonde girl, cuz you're with your man.
Yeah, yeah, you're with your man who
picked you. I like your whole demeanor.
You're a classy girl. You're independent
and intelligent, but classy. There's a
new breed of young girl under 25 that's
a special kind of skank I have never
seen in my life.
No, you know what I'm talking about. A
spe- See, MEN ARE HUNTERS. YOUR GUY
HUNTED YOU. YOUR LITTLE DUDE HUNTED YOU,
you know, with his little spear with the
six hairs on it. He hunted you.
Because men are hunters.
That's what I tell the girls now. I tell
my young girlfriends. I go, "Look, I'm
not telling you to be manipulative or
old-fashioned or play games, but a man
is a hunter. THERE'S A NEW KIND OF CHICK
THAT wears these Ed Hardy tank tops, and
they wear these giant platform shoes,
and they never eat, and they got the
wobbly little legs and the tank top and
the long blonde hair extensions to keep
them warm cuz they're so hungry cuz all
they ever Any The only thing that ever
goes in their MOUTH IS A COSMO chick tax
and random schlong, and they just
And they just what they They got a [\h__\h]
stamp when you see them by the pool, you
know, and they're like, "Ooh, a
bedazzled floss up their ass." Like
that.
Eventually they fall over. They're
always texting each other and losing
their balance cuz they're too hungry to
[\h__\h] talk, you know? They're just
>> [applause]
>> And they
You know, the wet Yeah.
I call them the wet kittens.
Have you all seen the wet kittens? And
I'm not going to lie to you, THERE'S A
LITTLE PART OF ME THAT'S JEALOUS OF the
wet kittens cuz they have a sexual
freedom I never KNEW. I ALWAYS WANTED to
be a puta, BUT MY MOM SPIED ON MY ASS.
And you see them, you know, and they're
just like, "Oh, like that. Like that."
And I'm going to TELL YOU RIGHT NOW, A
MAN, deep down in his heart, does not
want a promiscuous woman
for long.
Because women are not wired to be
promiscuous and men are not wired TO
LIKE IT. WHEN GUYS date strippers, I'm
back to you, beard boy.
You tell YOUR FRIENDS. YOU TELL YOUR
FRIENDS. It's going to be a problem
because it's not normal. I'm not
judging. If you're a stripper, I'm not
judging you. It's a job. You get a 1099,
you know what I mean? But it's not a
normal No little girl wakes up and
stretches and goes, "I'm going TO BE A
STRIPPER." NO, THAT'S BALLERINA gone
bad, okay?
That's going to be a problem. AND I TELL
THESE YOUNG GIRLS, GUYS ARE HUNTERS, you
know? If you're that girl, if you're
that DRUNK THAT "OH, I'M SO DRUNK. GIRLS
GONE WILD."
LIKE THAT. That's that I MEAN A GUY WILL
SNIFF YOU, you know, poke you around and
sniff you, but you're just sexual road
kill. She is so adorable. She's like,
"Don't look at me anymore. I'm not a
[\h__\h] I'm a good girl."
I can tell. What's your name,
sweetheart?
Sarah. May I ask how old you are?
20. So, you're a kid. You're a baby.
Yeah. I mean, when you were 10 years old
when Sex and the City came out. Your
whole life has been that sort of, you
know, it's a different world now. You
have so much freedom. Yeah, the girls
nowadays, their whole life is just dick
and shoes, dick and shoes, dick and
shoes, you know?
I think that's why women are crazier
than they've ever been before. We have
upped the ante on crazy. What's What's
your name, ma'am, with the white hair?
Marian. A pleasure to meet you, Marian.
Is it safe to say that you're over 38,
Marian?
Air quotes. Air quotes, Marian. Air
quotes, safe to say. Okay. So, you
remember a time when when women were
nurses, school teachers, if you left the
house at all, if you weren't a
stay-at-home mom. It was a different
world, right?
See?
She said absolutely. I think that's why
women are crazier than ever.
Yeah, and and the problem is women can
do anything, and I think that confuses
us because you can do anything, but you
can't do everything.
Ladies, you got to focus, okay? We are
making ourselves crazy. We think we have
to be perfect. You're nodding. You
understand. You write a checklist and
freak yourself out. You run around
trying to accomplish things. Men aren't
like that. Men are zen. They live in the
moment. They're too lazy and horny to
regret the past or fear the future.
They live in the now. Look at Mike
clapping. Yes.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO SAY LAZY. LET ME
SAY SIMPLE. SIMPLE, MONO FOCUS. They're
They're mono focused. Is that better?
Better, Mike? What's your name,
gorgeous?
Tamara. Okay, Tamara. Are you one of
those overachiever perfect soccer moms
that has to do everything just right?
>> I'm getting better.
>> No, that is such a lie. She says, "I'm
getting better."
I could almost hear your ass pucker
while you were lying to me.
Now, you're lying to me. Tamara, look me
right in the eye. Baby,
you can only focus on four things at a
time.
And don't take it personal that I say
four and I I'm not saying you Four
things is a lot of things. Pick four
things. Men can only focus on two, and
that's if you count tits as one, okay?
I mean it, Tamara.
You need to learn to relax, sister. I
can see you're nervous. You think too
much.
That's the biggest problem with women.
We think constantly. Again, we want that
approval, we want that support, we think
all the time cuz we try to make
ourselves useful. Cuz back in the
caveman day, there was a finite amount
of fur and fuel and fire, and that's how
women made themselves useful. We thought
all the time. And now we have handguns
and shake weights, and we can't stop.
You know,
TAMARA, LET ME BREAK it down for you.
The reason why we get so nervous and
upset is because we think we read these
magazines and we want to do everything
that's in the magazine, and we think and
we think and we wake up and we flip on
the turbines.
The ratio of thought to speech with a
woman, I have researched this, is 15 to
1.
Every time a woman utters a single
sentence, there were 15 potentials
spinning around her head at a high
speed.
Oh, yeah. Causing chaos. Picking up
houses and cows. And it's HARD TO THINK
THAT MUCH and not have to go to a dark
place.
15 to 1. That's what what I call EGT.
Evil girl thoughts, okay? If you think
that much, you're going to have evil
thoughts. You're going to freak yourself
out. You're going to upset yourself.
That's the monster of not good enough.
See, men are happy because the ratio of
thought to speech with a man, 0.5 to 1.
YOU HAVE HEARD YOUR HUSBAND SAY stupid
things, right?
He can't help it. He's not designed to
think complicated con- convoluted
thoughts. He's designed to kill [\h__\h] and
bring it home for your approval. He's
designed to spring up from behind a rock
and just nab it. It doesn't matter if
it's a goat or a paycheck. He wants to
bring it home to you and you say, "Good
boy. Let me touch your balls."
>> [applause]
>> And it's on you to understand this and
forgive him. He's going to say stupid
things. DDS, what I call dumb dude
statements. He's going to say stupid
things. He's going to be in the mall
with you and some skank's going to walk
by with booty shorts jacked up her ass.
You know exactly who I'm talking about.
And they always have those toes gripping
the front. What is that with strippers
with the toes? It's like they sleep
hanging from a pole. You know what I
mean? It's like what They're you
beautiful women with the most jacked up
feet, right? With chip toes You're
nodding. Yes, I've seen this. I don't
know any strippers, but I've heard. I uh
You got We got something to talk about.
But But I was saying, even you, as
intelligent as as as turned out, you
know, your your sartorial splendor, as
He's looking "Kick out of the casino.
What's sartorial splendor? Get out of
the casino, esta puta loca. You don't
entiendo nada."
What I'm saying is you're well dressed.
You put out a nice vibe. Even you are a
simple creature, right? When you go to
do a task, you're in the garage. Let's
say your wife said the right thing and
you're cleaning the garage. You're in
there cleaning the garage. She promised
you the Hummer and you're in there,
okay?
If your man is actually doing something
that you asked your man to do, leave him
alone until it's done.
WOMEN WILL POKE THEIR head in the garage
and go, "AND WHEN YOU'RE DONE with
that?"
That's like a computer, OKAY? TOO MANY
PROGRAMS OPEN WILL CRASH the man.
If you want the man to do something, you
ask him to do it, you wait till he's
completely done and leave him the hell
alone, and then when he comes in, no
matter how WELL
>> [screaming]
>> THEY ARE HIGH-FIVING EACH OTHER.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, SIR?
What's your name?
>> Ron.
>> Okay, Ron. What's your name? Tracy?
When he finishes the job, even if he
didn't do it the way you want, you just
tell him, "Sweetheart, it's amazing."
You encourage him. You encourage him.
You admire him. He'll do whatever you
want after a while. He'll be [\h__\h] up
the first eight times, but the ninth
it'll be perfect.
It's true.
And that's the way they want us to treat
them. It's the golden rule. When you
walk over to a man and you go, "How
would you like me to decorate the
house?"
Quietly.
"I don't care. Is there a color called
zip it blue? That's the color I want the
house, all right?"
Yeah, absolutely. Thank you. Now, I I
need to point out to you people because
it's becoming apparently obvious that I
am sweating like Nixon during the
debates, and I only know that cuz I've
seen it on YouTube. It is hot in San
Bernardino.
It is really hot. I mean, you're
wonderful people, and thank you for
being here, but it is super duper warm.
I was in Phoenix. Phoenix is super hot.
Super hot. I WAS BORN OH, HELL YEAH.
You been there, Mike?
You just moved from there. Good for you.
Yeah, to San Bernardino. Big
improvement, son.
Thanks for joining us on the other side
of hell. Thank you.
The desert in the middle, Phoenix, hell,
more hell here. I have
Yeah, no, it's super hot. And you know
what? This is a This is a a live taping,
but I could stop and say, "You know
what? Can we blow out? Can we take the
wet off of me?" I could do that. But you
know why I'm not going to do that?
Because I'm in the moment. I'm enjoying
you. I'm loving you.
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah.
>> [applause]
>> Thank you. Thank you.
It's true, CUZ I'M AN OLDER WOMAN. 20
YEARS AGO I WOULD HAVE BEEN FREAKING
OUT.
YEAH, I'M SO SWEATY. I DON'T LOOK SO
GOOD.
BUT WHEN you get older, you know what?
You enjoy the moment. You know the good
times. You know what? You remember Have
you ever been in a club, ladies, and you
meet A SUPER COOL MAGICAL GUY and you're
dancing and you're having such a cool
time and then you start to sweat a
little bit and you go in the bathroom
and you're trying to decide, do I keep
dancing or do I sit still? Spackle
repair, you know? Block spackle repair.
YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE DECISION, do I keep
going or do I stop? Me and my girlfriend
April we used to go to this club in
Houston. IF YOU THINK IT'S HOT HERE, let
me tell you something, the devil owns
Texas, all right?
He lives in hell and rents out Texas.
So hot AND IT'S A HUMID HOT. You never
get dry anywhere, no how, okay? It's
true. You put Gold Bond on your balls,
it just turns them into little nut
cutlets. That's just a
So hot.
But that's what I was talking about how
much women think. If a man is having a
good time, it never occurs to him to
say, I better stop. I'm starting to
sweat. I won't be as attractive. If a
man's having a good time, he'll just
dance and sweat dripping off his elbow
and he's just having a good time. Ladies
are like, I don't know. And then we have
to incorporate that dance move where we
can do the pit check. Am I starting to
smell?
You know, you do that move. Oh, yeah. I
am ripe. Yeah.
There's a dead moose in these pits,
baby. Stay back.
It's true.
I know it is. I wish these were jokes
and I didn't live them.
We need to remember to forget sometimes.
See, rise up out of ourselves. That's
one of the problems with women. Again,
sex is mental and it's very hard for
women to have a good sex. It is, because
it's not about the physical act. I'm
going to clue you in, guys. Women don't
really care about penis size. That's a
myth we get and we just made that up to
get even with y'all for the titty thing,
all right?
If you know what you're doing, you don't
have to have a big schlong, all right?
You just have to know, you know, the
wiggle. It's sort of like like
Greco-Roman wrestling with a boner. You
know what I mean? It's like if you got
the moves right
It's really more about trust. It's
really more about surrendering, about
letting yourself look bad and stupid
and sweaty and funky, you know? And when
you really trust a man, you'll put
yourself in that position and it's the
most delicious thing in the world. It
is. Cuz cuz it's true. Here That WAS A
GOOD LITTLE CLAP. YEAH.
HAS IT HAS IT CAN I ask you a question?
Has it been a little while since you had
that? Yeah, I could tell. And And you
know why? What What's your name,
gorgeous?
Tamara, awesome.
That's so cool. You guys could be
friends. And I like that you say Tamara,
because all Tammys are tramps.
Oh, it's true. If you know a Tammy,
she's a total [\h__\h] That's good.
Tamara's a good name. Tammy, not so
much. All Ambers eventually spin around
a pole, too. We were talking about that
earlier. Mike, confirmation? Amber?
Yeah.
Thank you. So, Tamara, here's what men
don't understand. Cuz when men go out,
there's no bad sex for a man. If there
was squirtin' and smokin', it was a good
time, you know what I mean? It was good.
But for women, there is bad sex. It's
true. The unknown and the unpleasured,
it does happen. When I was a road comic,
guys would hit on me and they'd be like,
"We've heard your act. You've been
married three times. It's not like
you're a virgin or anything." I'm like,
"Dude, let me tell you something. I got
a good book, water pressure, and
chocolate in my room. That's a sure
thing."
>> [cheering]
>> Yeah.
But it's true. Women Women would rather
live on the memory of good dick
than sully it with bad dick.
Women can SAVE A GOOD TIME LIKE a camel
in the hump right there.
Case we're going across a dick desert.
It's true. There's nothing we like
better than just kind of pulling it up,
you know, just pulling it up and
remembering a good time.
It's true. If you see a woman shudder in
church, she just pulled a little
something out of her [\h__\h] cooch.
Because when a woman gets it really
good, there's emotion involved. And we
can't help ourselves. When a woman gets
it really good, she will load chicks in
her car and drive and go, "Good dick
lives in that house right there."
Right
there.
We are proud.
Now, I know some of you single guys are
like, "HELP US OUT, MONIQUE. How do we
create a traffic jam in our cul-de-sac?
Please, help us out."
Here's how. It really comes down to
intention. It's what I was saying
earlier. It's emotional. A woman Women
are intuitive. We can feel your
intentions towards us. If it is your
intention to take care of a woman,
pleasure a woman, to give her a chance
to just kind of rise up out of herself
and relax and chill out. It's really not
just about the physical act. If a woman
trusts you and you force her to
surrender and you do it really awesome,
yeah. Let me explain. I'll use an
analogy cuz food is very big now.
There's a lot of foodies on the Food
Network. Think of sex as an enormous,
wonderful meal, you know? You got the
tablescape laid out, you know? That
equals you took a shower and soaked. And
you got the tablescape laid out. When a
woman comes through the door and you're
there, she knows. She knows you've
you've soaked, you've showered, cologne,
your hair's combed, you're smiling nice,
some candles, maybe some sexy music. Go
old school on her ass. A little Teddy
Pendergrass isn't bad.
Yeah. Little R Something with rhythm. A
little R&B is what I'm saying. Something
with some rhythm. Then the woman's all
like loosened up and into it, you know?
So So think of the things you do.
Kissing, fondling, touching the nippies,
you know? Yeah. Those are the side
dishes. Those are the side dishes, you
know? Think
She likes this. I'm going to come closer
to you. Yeah, you like She's LIKE
CLAPPING. TELL US MORE.
Think of oral sex as delicious potatoes
au gratin.
You get the potatoes right, you can hand
a chick beef jerky as the meat, okay?
She'll be all good, right? Yeah. What's
your name?
>> Sarah.
>> Sarah, I'm telling the truth, aren't I?
Yeah, cuz when you really make a woman
feel good and satisfied, and she's all
happy, I'll tell you how you know, cuz
she'll giggle. When you're all done with
a woman in a really good Tamara, you
remember the giggle? She'll be like,
like that, right? Look, you're giggling
NOW. YOU'RE REMEMBERING IT. IT'S COMING
RIGHT UP out of the cut, ain't it,
Tamara? Yeah.
Yeah, a woman will giggle and she'll be
like,
AND SHE'LL SCREAM, "STOP!
STOP! REALLY STOP THAT!" HIT YOU ON THE
TOP OF THE HEAD.
"I NEED IT!"
PULL YOUR HAIR A LITTLE.
IT IS HOT IN HERE, HUH?
I'M not helping the situation.
Rob, when you do that to a woman and she
giggles like that, she's what I call
dicky Ask her. I can tell. She's got her
head all down.
Have you been dicky drunk, haven't you?
It's the most intoxicating thing in the
world. That's why we giggle. Women
literally get dicky drunk. If you do it
right, SHE WILL STUMBLE OUT OF BED ALL
GOOFY AND SMACK INTO A WALL that's been
there 10 years.
Rubbing her forehead.
Smiling at you.
>> [applause]
>> Yeah.
She'll be like, "Now hurt in two
places."
But when somebody really, really loves
you, it's kind of like a LoJack on your
brain. You know, there's just so far
down the road of depressed and freaked
out I can get and then I remember I have
a good man and he picked me.
I did the hard thing. Now it's up to me
to try and remain the person that he
picked. See, men Thank you. That's a
nice thank you.
Try to remain that person.
Are you with me now, machete?
Cuz you're looking all somber like this
is good stuff.
I wish I'd have brought some of my kids
and their mothers.
>> [cheering]
>> No, it's true. I have the most wonderful
life now. I'm so grateful. I hope I gave
you some stuff. I tell people, if I made
you laugh, that's really, really my gig.
I really want to make you laugh. But I
tell people, if I if I made you think,
that's good. That's a really good thing
cuz you go home and you think of some
stuff. The ladies, you're going to go
home, you're going to suck it in, you're
going to buy the expensive panties. I
know they feel like a cheesy grater, BUT
THEY WON'T BE ON LONG.
And and that's that's the thing. If if I
made you think, great. If I made you
laugh, that's the real deal because
laughter is the salve that keeps reality
from scarring, you know what I mean? And
and then I tell people, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
AND GRATITUDE IS THE PERFECT concealer
for everything that went wrong.
Absolutely. I'm so grateful for my life.
I have a great life. I have great
relationships now. Me and my mom, we so
get along, you know, after heartbreak
and homos, she and I just like we're
like this right there.
I was heartbroken and and we're we're
tight. It's a it's a good thing and my
brothers, I have the best brothers in
the world and you know, I just have a
great life. I miss my dog, Vinnie
Mascatelli. I had a dog when I started
comedy and I wish he could be here
tonight. You know, he was my road guy
when I started out being a comedian,
that little dog went everywhere with me.
He was totally my little dude, man. 17
years I had that dog. From my first gig.
Yeah. This is
Vinnie Mascatelli, my little Italian
dog.
Isn't that great, Tamara? You People
will say, "How do you know your dog's
Italian?" He's little, he's hairy, he's
macho, he's possessive.
Didn't know he was little, hairy, macho,
and possessive.
Shows everybody his magenta crayon.
He's a little lover, that Vinnie.
I hope my grandma's looking down. She'd
be so happy. My grandma, stubborn ass
woman. My grandma, stubborn.
She couldn't hear for [\h__\h] She's deaf.
But she wouldn't get a hearing aid, so
we'd have to scream ALL THE TIME.
"ABUELITA!"
YOU KNOW, WITH STRAINED VOCAL CORDS.
YOU KNOW WHY SHE GOT A HEARING AID
FINALLY? BINGO.
Not for us.
So she could hear the bingo caller.
The bingo caller WOULD BE LIKE, "B-23."
You would hear it before the hearing
aid. "Que?"
Now she'd be like, "B-23. Gon' you." And
I'd go,
"That's a cuss word for I don't have
B-23. Yeah."
So finally got her a hearing aid. She
goes up to my mother. She's like, "My
E." That's My mother's name is Margie,
but in Spanish, "My E."
"My E, este aparato, my hearing aid,
this thing gives me gas."
My mother's like, "No, Mama, you always
had gas. You just couldn't hear
yourself."
Yeah.
That's the kind of people I come from,
stubborn, delusional, wonderful people.
My mom, so adorable, so polite, so cute.
My mom, I took my mother to Vegas for
the first time. My mother had never been
to Vegas. 69th birthday, I go, "Mommy,
you're going to Vegas." And my mother
sees, "Esta mujer, look at these women."
She's freaked out, you know, you know
what goes around Vegas with the floss
and all of that, you know, all that
business. Mama's like, "Oh my god, are
those women professionals?"
My mother can't even say hooker, she's
too polite.
To my mother, it would be a pedestrian
sperm engineer.
She's so decent, so cute. I took her to
Vegas, she loved it so much. She's so
cute. You know what I'm really proud of,
too? How many And again, I don't mean to
pander, but we are in San Bernardino.
How many of my Latino brothers and
sisters are here?
Clap, [cheering] make some noise. Clap,
clap. Thank you.
It's a funny thing cuz my mom's gotten
to that phase where she You can see
she's trying to get along with me for a
couple of reasons. And she just finally
came right out and said it the other
day. She's like, "You would never put me
in a home, right, honey?"
Cuz that's women's greatest fear.
Women's greatest fear is that they're
going to end up in their daughter's
garage getting fat on cat food, you
know?
It's true. It's It's probably a good
reason I don't have a daughter. I'll
just be in some random garage eating cat
food, but
But one of the things I'm really proud
of is that in a In English, you know,
you have convalescent home, assisted
senior living, you have you have all of
these names. It's Spanish people, think
about it, there is no word for old folks
home in Spanish.
There isn't cuz we can't afford them
anyway.
We just have to keep them. And don't
worry, Mom and Dad.
The Sumners from Apple Valley,
>> [laughter]
>> I'll have a very nice garage converted
apartment for both of you, okay?
Absolutely, you can count on it. I see
everybody fanning themselves. You know
what? Thank you, I've got to mention it
again. Thank you for sitting through the
heat, all right? I mean, it is hot. It's
not lizard exploding hot, but it's
I was going to try and get a little
action in my green room with my
boyfriend after the show, but I'd have
to rinse off. It's uh
I got Yeah, an hour talking to you
people, I've definitely got a little
swamp puss going on. It's uh yeah.
Yeah.
It's marinated.
That's a man right there.
>> [cheering]
>> Spray a little Febreze in your pits,
baby. I got a boner. Let's go.
I uh I'm going to start to wrap it up
now because there's so many of you that
I want to make sure I say goodnight to
Ron and his woman. Make sure you know
the drill now, okay? You know what to
do. He does the right thing. What are
you going to rub?
You're going to rub
>> Everything.
And you're going to do it like you mean
it, right? Throw your back in it. Don't
take your man for granted. There's a lot
of hussies out there.
There are a lot of hussies. There's a
different kind of woman out there now.
They're They're aggressive and they
don't even know how to really enjoy
something, you know? Huh?
>> They can't cook.
>> They can't cook. This is now turning
into an open forum where people just
yell at each other.
They can't cook. THEY WON'T RUB YOUR
BALLS. WHAT DO THEY WANT TO DO? THEY
JUST WANT to be out in the workplace.
Oh. I'm not a very good cook, but that's
funny you should say that. When you
really love somebody and they make you
happy, you will try things you've never
done before.
>> Like that trick?
>> Yeah.
>> Here's the thing. True story. I had not
cooked for a very, very long time. Uh I
had Unfortunately, I I suffered a burn
when I was younger and it freaked me out
and I didn't cook for a lot of years.
And then it's true. And then when I met
my man, I thought, you know what? It's
been a long time and part of that's an
excuse. So I decided I said, you know
what? I'm going to learn to cook. I'm
going to learn to cook and I'm going to
cook something delicious and I'm going
to make pancakes.
But here's the cool thing, ladies. Take
the pancakes a step further. Here's what
you do. You make pancakes and then you
tell your man, "Lay down, face down."
And then you get some butter.
And you butter each cheek.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then you put the pancakes. Let them
cool down. You don't want to scald his
ass.
This is the perfect combination, sex and
maple syrup.
And then you put your hair back in a
ponytail, you put your hands behind your
back, and you start eating the pancakes.
And then you start licking the maple
syrup.
And you'll know your man's really having
a good time when he'll move a cheek and
go, "You missed a spot."
We call that Saturday.
I'm going to give you my three best
pieces of advice. Number one, love hard.
Your heart is a muscle, okay? Even if
you're loving the wrong person, consider
it cardio for your spirit, okay?
And you can always learn something, even
if you're loving the lowest form of
life. Believe me, I know.
Number two, forgive harder. That's the
one that really freaks people out.
Forgive everyone. Forgive his
ex-girlfriend, the skank.
If it wasn't for her, you wouldn't have
him. And believe me, girls, I try to
tell the guys, "Women are a little
insecure. Every woman you were with
before is a [\h__\h] and you regret it,
okay?"
And number three, get as happy as you
can as fast as you can. That It's
nobody's job but yours. Thank you. Good
night. God bless you.
>> [cheering]